LEANDRO IBARRA

Team Leader / Full Stack Developer

- +54 341 3243616
- lea14_9@hotmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/leandro-ibarra/
- github.com/leandroibarra/
- Argentina, SF

EDUCATION

University Systems Analyst Instituto Politécnico Superior 2010 - 2014

KNOWLEDGE AND SKILLS

ActiveCollab, AJAX, Angular,
AngularJS, API Rest, Apache,
ASP, AWS, Bitbucket, Bootstrap,
Client/Server side templating,
CSS, Eloquent, Git, GitHub,
GitLab, HTML, Ionic, JavaScript,
Jira, jQuery, JSON, LAMP,
Laravel, LESS, Linux, Lumen,
MEAN, Microsoft SQL Server,
MongoDB, MySQL, NestJS,
NodeJS, PHP, phpMyAdmin,
PostgreSQL, SASS, SCRUM, Slim
Framework, SQL, SQL Server,
SVN, Trello, TypeScript,
WordPress, XAMPP.

PROFILE

Systems Analyst with extensive experience as a Full Stack Developer and Team Leader in different software companies. Solid performance in contact with clients, identifying needs, preparing documentation and solving problems. Self-taught, curious, proactive, with knowledge of agile methodologies. Proven ability to lead teams aimed at generating a collaborative work culture. Mastery of technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, AngularJS, Angular, NodeJS, Express, NestJS, PHP, WordPress, Laravel, SQL, SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, among others.

EXPERIENCE

O July 2020 - October 2023 Whyline - Clear

Team Leader / Full Stack Developer

Development and maintenance of web systems using NodeJS, NestJS, AngularJS, Angular, TypeScript. MongoDB non-relational databases. Use of services in AWS. SCRUM methodology with an agile mindset. Management and monitoring of tasks and incidents with Jira. Leadership of interdisciplinary teams on multiple projects.

July 2018 - June 2020 Puntoini Software

Full Stack Developer

Back-end development with PHP, NodeJS and Express; and front-end with Ionic and Angular. Development and maintenance of sites with Laravel and WordPress. Relational databases MySQL and MariaDB and non-relational databases such as MongoDB. Version control with Git, GitLab and Bitbucket. SCRUM methodology. Project management: tasks/features, bug relief and resolution, technical documentation, user manual, product demonstrations.

August 2012 - June 2018 Dynamic Mind

Full Stack Developer

Development and implementation of REST APIs with PHP, Slim Framework, NodeJS and Express. Development and maintenance of sites with AngularJS, Angular, Ionic and WordPress. Administration and optimization of relational databases MySQL and PostgreSQL and non-relational databases such as MongoDB. Version control with Git and GitLab. SCRUM methodology. Project management with tools like ActiveCollab and Trello.

January 2012 - July 2012 Oh!STUDIO Soluciones en internet

Web Developer

Programming, development and maintenance of applications using PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, institutional websites, development and maintenance of WordPress plugins. Maintenance of e-learning applications with ASP and SQLServer. Version control with SVN.